VU NGOC QUANG

Penetration Tester/ Application Security Engineer

Gender: Male **DOB:** 11/03/1997

Phone: (+84)-909110397 **Email:** quangvn777@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/quangvu11

Address: Hanoi, Vietnam

ABOUT

I've had 4+ years experience in Cyber Security field, as a full-time and professional Penetration Tester. My job was focus on conducting penetration testing, security assessment on various targets such as Web Applications, Moblie Applications, Systems. etc; consulting security solutions and ensure every clients' products is safe from attackers. Apart from Penetration Testing, I also worked as a team member of Threat Intelligence Team, focused on training Cyber Security Awareness for employees.

EXPERIENCE

VinCSS - Cyber Security Services - member of Vingroup

Penetration Testing/ Application Security | November, 2019 - Present

- Key Responsibilities:
 - Performing Blackbox/Whitebox/Graybox manual and automated penatration testing across public and private networks on various targets including Web Application, Mobile Application, Systems, Services, Micro Services, API(s), Firmware, etc.
 - Performing source-code review for finding vulnerabilities.
 - Performing Security Audit and Review on Applications, Server, Infrastructure,
 Database, etc.
 - Offering remediation and consulting on security issues.
 - Live-working and technical communicating with clients, developers to thoroughly fixing existed vulnerabilities as well as hardening methods if necessary.
 - Verifying fixed results of clients, as well as provide post-recommendation if necessary.
 - Consulting on security solutions, implementing information security policies.
 - Making final report on findings, offering final conclusion to managers and clients if necessary.
- Side Responsibilities:
 - Making content for Cyber Security Awareness newsletters, papers, emails, etc.
 - Making content for Cyber Security Training Course.
 - Updating documents if necessary.

- Key Achievments:
 - Participated in more than 140 different Penetration Testing, Security Audit,
 Security Assessment projects, across various different fields including:
 technology, medication, financial, commercial, AI, housing, CMS, etc.
 - Discoverd more than 200 security flaws and vulnerabilities, 45% of which are rated as Critial and High severity.

Internship | Early 2018 - October, 2019

- Researching modern attack techniques, strategies.
- Hands-on practice as a red team, performing practical training on Ethical Hacking,
 Penetration Testing.
- Supporting on live projects.

SKILLS

- Solid experience of Web Application penetration testing including perform pentesting with OWASP standard, follow procedure and methodology, able to find and exploit various vulnerabilities.
- Ability to perform post-exploitation on Linux, Windows if necessary.
- Ability to review source-code to address security flaws and vulnerabilities (PHP, Java, JS, C#, etc.) as well as dymanic testing.
- Ability to assess/calculate risk based on threats, vulnerabilities. Support and consult with product and development teams in the area of application security.
- Intermediate on penetration testing on Mobile Application, finding common vulnerabilities as well as API(s) and services testing with both static and dynamic testing.
- Highly experienced on tools of penetration testing such as: Kali-Linux, BurpSuite, MobSF, Postman, Metasploit, Nmap, Nessus, Acunetix, Empire, AppScan, etc.
- Backgound/Understanding of Azure AD Security: Attack Strategies and Defensive Measures.
- OSINT
- Basic programming with Python, PHP, JS.
- Efficient Team-working.
- Advanced English (4 skills).

EDUCATION

2015 - 2018 | University of Science and Technology Hanoi

Bachelor of Computer Science